Inside the church and will be streamed out for people
to watch them. It's not as a reminder to say that some,
the viruses have a massive impact on people's daily lives.
And their routines with is also the massive
economic impacts. Because room at this time of year
would be filled with tourists traveling that Easter break.
But of course, the hotels, shops and restaurants are shot.
American tourists are being told to stay away.
The city's, you know, pretty much empty objects in long
looked down and not to set to continue further.
Okay, Michelle. Thanks.
It was his gun is today coming out
the some heroes facing customers every day.