Now that several countries in Europe have passed the peak
of their Coronavirus outbreaks. Authorities have started
to address when they might start easing lockdowns.
In France, finance minister Bruno le Maire
said restaurants and bars won't open before June.
But the sector will receive
more financial support in May.
"We plan to open in the best sanitary
conditions possible to reassure customers and employees."
A guide to good practice is backed by a legal framework,
a review clause and then a final decision
twenty-eight of May. What all be needed
to have a precise reopening date for cafes, restaurants
and bars.
For Belgian restaurants and bars will stay shut
throughout May as well. But prime minister Sophie Wilmés,
announced on Friday that some shops will be allowed
to open up again on May eleventh.
With schools to follow, opening on May eighteenth.
The Czech Republic has experienced a much lighter outbreak
compared to many of its neighbours
and from Monday Czechs will be allowed to leave home
whenever they want and gather in groups of ten.
EU citizens will even be allowed to visit for business.