Now that several countries in Europe have passed the peak
of their Coronavirus outbreaks.
Authorities have started to address when they might start
easing lockdowns. In France finance.
Minister Bruno le Maire, said restaurants
and bars won't open before June,
but the sector will receive more financial support in May.
We plan to open in
the best sanitary conditions possible to reassure customers
and employees. A guide to good practice is backed by a legal
framework, a review clause
and that a final decision towards the end of May.
What all be needed to have a precise reopening date for cafes,
restaurants and bars. For Belgian restaurants
and bars will stay shut throughout May as well.
But prime minister Sophie Wilmés,
as announced on Friday that some shops will be allowed
to open up again on may eleventh.
with schools to follow opening on May eighteenth.
The Czech Republic has experienced a much lighter outbreaks
compared to many of its neighbors
and for Monday checks will be allowed to leave home whenever
they want and gather in groups of ten.
EU Citizens will even be allowed to visit for business.