Inside the church and would be streamed out for people
to watch so... That is a reminder also that the
the viruses have a massive impact on people's daily lives.
And their routines with this also the massive
economic impacts. Because Rome at this time of year
would be filled with tourists traveling there full the Easter break.
But of course, the hotels are shut, the restaurants are shot.
And tourists have been told to stay away.
The city's, you know, pretty much empty and it's in
locked down and that is to set to continue further.
Okay, Michelle. Thanks.
You're watching Sky News Today coming up
Happy to help. The unsung heroes facing customers every day on a shop floor.